COLIN BURGESS

211 N Williamson St, Atlanta, MO 63530 · (719)-351-7456

CRB5825@Gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/c0c0b/

C0C0Barbet.github.io

Experienced in various languages, focused largely on C#, C/C++, and Python. Accomplished at building connections in team settings for improved information flow and production. Excellent communication skills combined with an analytical and attentive nature. Looking forward to problem solving plus developing scalable applications and software.

EDUCATION

MAY 2018

ASSOCIATES OF PSYCHOLOGY, MOBERLY AREA COMMUNITY COLLEGE

DECEMBER 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF ALASKA ANCHORAGE

EXPERIENCE

10/2021 - 01/2022

JAVA FULL STACK DEVELOPER, TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES

- Hired and began training to become a Java full stack developer on October 11th, 2021.
- Training is set to be completed December 22nd and consists of Angular and Node.js with a refresher of java, SQL, and JDBC.

01/2022 - 03/2022

ASSOCIATE APPLICATION DEVELOPER, OFFICE OF ADMINISTRATION ITSD-DNR

- Gained advanced professional understanding and coding abilities in Java.
- Developed greater problem-solving skills related to investigation of server issues.
- Supported Missouri's Department of Natural Resources web applications through STRUTS and Spring development.

03/2022 - PRESENT

APPLICATION DEVELOPER, OFFICE OF ADMINISTRATION ITSD-DNR

- deepened my abilities as a programmer and gained even greater knowledge application development
- Became the lead support on a few applications where I actively and efficiently implemented bug fixes as well as enhancements
- Gained a greater understanding of SQL, STRUTS 2, and Spring Boot.

PROJECTS

TOWER OF HANOI REDUX

While in my senior year of University I enrolled in a computer graphics course which tasked me
with creating some application regarding graphics. I eventually decided upon the traditional
Tower of Hanoi game which I would build in Unity. After the course had finished, I was left with a

rudimentary version of the game and felt compelled to continue my work. Over time I improved the aesthetic and functions of the game leading to what I currently have displayed on my online portfolio. That game is still not as complete as I would like however as I worked on it entirely on my own, I am quite happy! Tower of Hanoi Redux is available on the Google Play Store and is hosted on itch.io.

MY FIRST GAME JAM 2021

• In July of 2021, I was left with free time while job searching and noticed itch.io was hosting a beginner's game jam. I decided to reach out to a friend and try our luck with a simple 2D platformer. The experience was fun and helped me learn how to work in a team and lead as my friend had little experience with Unity. As the game was made in two weeks, forcing me out of my comfort zone. This game is hosted on itch.io and is also available on my online portfolio.

LANGUAGES AND SKILLS

- C# (.NET)
- C++
- Java
- Python

- HTML, CSS, JSP, JavaScript
- Some Angular/Node.js Training
- Spring Boot
- SQL and DB2

ACTIVITIES

Throughout my post-secondary education, I worked on various projects using the Unity game engine and dabbled in the Unreal engine. In my free time I still like to spend time working on various projects in Unity, Unreal, Java.